RAHUL VAIDYA

Rawatpura Colony, Mathpuraina, Raipur · 9131354481 rahulvaidya920820@gmail.com

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, and architectural systems research. Now having 5+ years of experience in web technologies such as JavaScript, Typescript, Vue, Angular, Node JS and Laravel. Also, I have gained experience in Arcgis, WinJS, React-Native technology. I am always eager to learn new technologies which enhance my skills.

EXPERIENCE

APR 2021 – TILL NOW

PROGRAMMER-CHHATTISGARH INFOTECH PROMOTION SOCIETY (CHIPS)

Working in web application development.

- 1. Worked for some state government projects.
- 2. Provide a solution to agriculture department through which they are capable to run their cow dunk related scheme smoothly.
- 3. Provide a solution to department in which they are monitoring the activity of Gauthans.
- 4. Working on a project for tribal department in which providing a solution to fetch and monitor the land disputes as well as village boundary data.
- Portals are developed using technology such as Angular, Laravel, NodeJS, MySql, NoSQL, Vue JS.
- 6. Recognized and appreciated by "Agriculture Production Commissioner CG State".

MAY 2020 - MAR 2021

PROGRAMMER-CG SECURITY SERVICES

Working in web application development.

- 1. Worked on some client side projects (In CHiPS).
- 2. Provide a solution for state government to monitor different schemes in a single dashboard.
- 3. Portal is developed using technology such as Angular, Laravel, CI.

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER-QOLARIS DATA INDIA LTD

Working in web application development.

- 1 Worked on a project which is used for procurement management industries.
- 2 The objective of this project is to provide solutioning to stakeholders so that they can analysis their business profit and manage their cost to achieve their goal.

JUNE 2019 – DEC 2019

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER- NIC (NATIONAL INFORMATICS CENTER) RAIPUR, CHHATTISGARH

Working in web application development.

- 1 Worked on a project which is used by a school education department.
- 2 The objective of this project is student's scholarship will be transferred through digital payment system. For this we were doing payment through DSC certificate and achieved this benchmark with the use of PFMS payment system.
- 3 Through this project I have gained experience on SQL server 2012 and ASP.NET.

SEP 2017 – JUNE 2019

PROJECT TRAINEE – GIS (DEVELOPER), CHHATTISGARH INFOTECT PROMOTION SOCITY (CHIPS)

RAIPUR, CHHATTISGARH

Working in web GIS domain.

- 1. Developed a web GIS application for an Industrial Corporation of Chhattisgarh Government. The geoportal is live now and used by public user. This portal was developed with technologies Arcgis Javascript 3.x, Arcserver 10.x, javascript, jQuery, CSS, HTML5.
- 2. Developed a web geoportal for Water Resource Department, Chhattisgarh. This geoportal is also live and used by department people. Developed this portal using technologies such as Arcserver 10.x, Arcgis javascript 3.x library, javascript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, PHP, and MySql. Similar application with minimum changes is also developed for the district collectors of Chhattisgarh and other departments.
- 3. Worked on CTOPPS application, this application was used during election of Assembly constituency and parliamentary constituency for monitoring the election activity.

JUL 2016 – AUG 2017

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER, GLOBALLOGIC INDIA

Worked in front-end development.

- 1. Worked in IPTV domain for one Canada based telecom company using technology such as **Angular JS (ver-1).**
- 2. Worked in IOT project which is for a USA based company. It was a hybrid application developed by using **React-Native.**
- 3. Developed a social application for X-Box one using **WinJS**.
- 4. Worked on developing a web application Bulletin Board. It is a dashboard application which is used by the company employee. This application is developed using Angular 2, NodeJS and NoSQL.

EDUCATION

S. No.	Examination	University	Subjects	Session	Percentage	Passing Division
1.	MCA	CSVTU, Bhilai.	-	2013-16	74%	First
2.	BCA	PRSU, Raipur.	-	2010-13	65%	First
3.	12 th	CGBSE	PCM	2009	70%	First
4.	10 th	CGBSE	-	2007	66%	First

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Skill	Skill Subcategory		
UI Development	Arcgis web development, jQuery, React-Native, Polymer.		
Javascript/Typescript	AngularJS, Angular, VueJS, ReactJS, WinJS		
HTML/CSS	CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap, Materialized CSS.		
Server-Side Scripting	NodeJS, ASP.NET, Laravel, CodeIgniter		
Database	NoSql, ArcServer, GeoServer, MySQL, PostgreSQL		

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Rahul Vaidya
Father Name: Siddharth Vaidya
Date of birth: 20th Aug 1992

Qualification(s): MCA
Marital status: Married